# JORDAN A. I. MAHARAJ

#6, CHURCH STREET. LA ROMAIN · (868) 479 0865 <u>Jordan.maharaj@my.uwi.edu</u> / jordanmaharaj4@gmail.com

Analytical, organized and detail oriented individual, with prior experience in customer service, tutoring and laboratory work. Collaborative team player who places importance on the quality and reliability of their work.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### PART-TIME SALES CLERK – SUMMER VACATION

2017 – 2021 - KEITH KHAN'S BOOK STORE, NAVET ROAD, SAN FERNANDO - 219 9775

2022 - 2022 - MOHAMMED'S BOOKSTORE - 657 9613

- Assisted customers with acquiring items on the booklist.
- Pricing of books.
- Checking delivery of books and stationery.

#### **PART-TIME PRIVATE TUTOR**

2020 - PRESENT

REFERENCE - NADIA MOHAMMED (730-3270) - PARENT OF STUDENTS

- Tutored SEA students in Mathematics.
- Tutored Secondary School Students in Mathematics, Biology and Chemistry.

## **MEDICAL LABORATORY TECHNICIAN**

FEBRUARY 2023 - JANUARAY 2024

- Performed blood tests for patients in the departments of hematology, biochemistry, and microbiology.
- Issued results to patients and doctors urgently and accurately.
- Performed maintenance of various machines.
- Analyzed control values each shift to ensure the reliability of results.

#### **EDUCATION**

#### BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN BIOCHEMISTRY AND BIOLOGY,

UNIVERSITY OF THE WEST INDIES SAINT AUGUSTINE- 2019- 2022

ASJA BOYS COLLEGE SAN FERNANDO 2017 - 2019

CAPE UNIT 1 CAPE UNIT 2

BIOLOGY BIOLOGY CHEMISTRY

COMMUNICATION STUDIES CARIBBEAN STUDIES

ENVIRONMENTAL SCIENCE ENVIRONMENTAL SCIENCE

ASJA BOYS COLLEGE SAN FERNANDO 2012 – 2017

CARIBBEAN SECONDARY EDUCATION CERTIFICATE - CSEC

**MATHEMATICS** 

**ENGISH A** 

**SOCIAL STUDIES** 

**BIOLOGY** 

**CHEMISTRY** 

**PHYSICS** 

**GEOGRAPHY** 

**ADDITONAL MATHEMATICS** 

#### **SKILLS**

- Proficiency in Microsoft programs (Word, Excel and Office).
- Compliance
- Detail oriented
- Multi-tasking

- Excellent oral and written communication
- Adaptability
- Organizational skills

## **ACTIVITIES & INTERESTS**

- Football
- Basketball
- Chess

- Solving puzzles
- Reading
- Experiencing different cultures